Finding Aid for Office for the Study of Automotive Transportation (University of Michigan) records, 1981-1991
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Office for the Study of Automotive Transportation (University of Michigan)records 1981-1991
University of Michigan. Office for the Study of Automotive Transportation.
1 linear foot
89504 Bimu C551 2
Records, 1981-1987, of the Office for the Study of Automotive Transportation (OSAT), a unit of the University of Michigan Transportation Research Institute (UMTRI); include correspondence, newsletters and other published materials, subject files, and other records relating to the automotive industry of the United States, especially to its competition with Japan.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The records were transferred from the Office for the Study of Automotive Transportation (donor no. 7506 ).
The record group is open without restriction.
Founded in 1981, the Office for the Study of Automotive Transportation (OSAT) is a unit of the University of Michigan Transportation Research Institute (UMTRI) that describes and analyzes the automotive industry's current developments and future directions. Its overall objectives are to provide research and analysis, information resources, and communication forums that meet the evolving needs of the international automotive and related industries. In addition, OSAT serves as an interface and resource for industry stakeholders, including manufacturers, suppliers, retailers, labor, scholars, government, the media, and the general public.
Office for the Study of Automotive Transportation (University of Michigan)records include correspondence, newsletters and other published materials, subject files, and other records relating to the automotive industry of the United States, especially to its competition with Japan.
Subjects:
Automobile industry and trade--Japan.; Automobile industry and trade--United States.; Japan.
- Records
  - Auto in Michigan Project Newsletter, 1985-1988, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Automotive News World Congress, 1991 (Box 1)
  - Brochures (Box 1)
  - Budget, 1981 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Delphi Forecasts (Box 1)
  - Delphi Forecasts and Analysis of the U. S. Automotive Industry in the 1980s, printed version and 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Delphi IV, volumes 1-3 (Box 1)
  - Delphi V, volumes 1-3 (Box 1)
  - "Energy Related Motor Vehicle Research at the University of Michigan" (Box 1)
  - Japanese/U.S. Automotive Industry Conference (Box 1)
  - Office for the Study of Automotive Transportation Conference (Box 1)
  - Organizational (Box 1)
  - South Korea's Industrial Environment (Box 1)
  - Task Force on University/Industry Interaction (Box 1)
  - Published Materials (Box 1)
  - Notebook, "The Automotive Leadership Challenge" (Box 1)